THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
GANGLIM OUTPOST
Man, it's cold.
Jeez, are the seasons here
always this extreme?
It feels like it's either
summer or winter.
You saw how intense the mood
at the outpost was, right?
They were tearing everyone a new one.
Still, I thought it'd be fine
since the Outpost Commander
came back okay.
Seriously, do you think there will ever be
a quiet day at this darn outpost? Oh, man.
Remember how much it sucked
when the typhoon hit in the summer?
You think something like that
won't happen again
if it snows a ton this winter?
I'm worried about the mess
Ganglim Outpost will be in without me.
Where did he go?
- What are you doing?
- Oh, it's nothing.
How can I get discharged
and leave you behind?
Open the door. Quick.
- Okay.
- Man, it's cold.
Hero.
Protect the Ganglim Outpost.
Ganglim Outpost is in danger
of being shut down.
To protect the endangered Ganglim Outpost
win the division cooking competition.
Failure will result in the closure
of the Ganglim Outpost
and The Chef's Path will also disappear.
Until the Ganglim Outpost Shutdown
you have 14 days remaining.
This is an announcement
from the Administrative Office.
All personnel in the outpost.
Please report
to your respective barracks immediately.
GANGLIM OUTPOST SHUTDOWN D-14
Thank you for your hard work.
Now that everyone's here,
including Kang Seong-jae
I'll get to the announcement.
Jeez, what is it? Spit it out.
Did Master Sergeant Park
give you another weird order?
Well... The outpost is being shut down
so they're pulling everyone back
to the battalion.
Shut down?
- Yes, that's right.
- Shut down, you say?
The Outpost Commander said
she'd explain the details
later this evening
and told us not to get worked up about it.
Isn't this actually a good thing?
There are so many inconveniences
living at the outpost.
Yes, things are always breaking.
We're short-staffed
and there's too much to do.
Still, it'll be better at the battalion
than here, right?
I'm so close to being discharged,
and now they're yanking us around?
So annoying.
Gosh, finally.
This frustrating outpost life
is finally over. It's over.
Win the division cooking competition.
Failure will result in the closure
of the Ganglim Outpost.
The closure of the outpost.
Win the cooking competition.
The cooking competition...
Welcome.
- Hero.
- Private Kang Seong-jae.
Looking back
everything started here
at Ganglim Outpost.
SPICY BEAN SPROUT SOUP
REFRESHING!
- Perfect! This is delicious!
The mess hall, once filled
with disorganized rations
and tons of food waste
was filled with delicious smells
and the sounds
of trays being scraped clean
and that might have been
because Ganglim was here.
Ganglim!
- Forever!
Hero. Mess Hall Satisfaction Rating
has increased.
If the outpost disappears
I'll disappear too.
EPISODE 11
What competition?
It's called
the division cooking competition.
Gosh, the outpost
is about to be shut down.
What's this about a cooking competition?
Hey, and look. There's nothing here.
You came to talk about entering
some competition that doesn't even exist.
What?
What's this?
Seong-jae, what was that?
29TH DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
A team of three?
Kang Seong-jae.
- I don't think this is a good idea.
- But I really have to do this.
Our outpost is closing in just 13 days.
Do you think the Company Commander
will approve it?
It's obvious he won't.
And a three-person team?
There's no one else to join.
Still, could you please just print out
an application form for me?
We have two weeks until
the scheduled transfer of the soldiers.
The gear and supplies
will be moved after that.
You've all been briefed on that, right?
Yes. I've already contacted
the supplies department
so we just need to coordinate
the schedule.
Did the Company Commander say anything?
Well, he just said
- to handle it ourselves.
- Gosh, this is so frustrating.
He must be busy getting ready
to transfer with the Battalion Commander.
I'm only saying this
because I'm so frustrated.
Did you see
the comprehensive inspection report?
Deteriorating facilities
and negligent management?
They wrote it as if we just completely
mismanaged the outpost.
That's just an excuse.
I'm sure he's displeased with me.
Because he found out that I was looking
into the food supply company.
I'm sorry to have put you
in this position.
No, Outpost Commander.
You were just doing your job.
That's right. Yes.
- All right, let's get to it.
- Yes.
Didn't you have a soft spot for Min-gu?
That's why people are saying
it makes no sense that you didn't know.
Of course, I did my best
to smooth things over.
- But you know
- Salute...
that everyone gets uncomfortable
when things get this messy.
Yes, sir.
Again, I apologize
for causing you concern.
Salute!
- The Regimental Commander's calling?
- I can't believe how many people
are suffering because of Min-gu.
Actually, you, Seok-ho
suffered the most cleaning up the mess.
I've also made sure the outpost officers
won't say anything more.
Seok-ho.
Now you really seem
like one of my own men.
You've worked hard. Should we go get
something good to eat?
- Yes, sir.
- All right.
MILITARY CONFIDENTIAL
You're not serious, are you?
I am completely serious.
Hey, how long do you expect me
to stay in the army?
I have to go home soon.
I need to take my terminal leave, don't I?
I calculated it, and there won't be
any problem with your discharge...
What am I, your security blanket
or something?
Why can't you just leave me alone?
But I thought if I entered with you
we'd make a good team,
so that's why I asked.
A good team? Yes, right.
That's because I'm always the one
accommodating you.
- Can't you please do it?
- No means no.
Oh, well...
I think the prize money is
one million won.
Jeez. Nothing works without me, does it?
Nothing at all.
I get eight, and you get two.
But the requirement is
a three-person team.
Three people?
Fine. I get eight, and you get one.
Let's go find our other one.
Kang Seong-jae, follow me.
Why does the one have to be you?
Excuse me?
You heard him correctly.
We desperately need your knife skills
for this cooking competition.
With your skills, Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol
you're better than most soldiers
in the Officers' Mess.
Are you saying
I'm better than those guys
in the Officers' Mess?
In terms of speed, accuracy,
and everything
I don't think you'd be outmatched
in any way, sir.
You think he's going
to fall for that kind of lip service?
Hey, he's not all that.
Can't you hear them
shuttering the outpost?
Who's thinking about a competition
in a situation like this?
I know. Since they're suddenly
shuttering the outpost
don't you want to finish on a high note?
- Don't you get it?
- This is my last chance.
Will you really not do it?
No, I mean...
It's not like we're guaranteed to win
just by entering.
And even if we somehow win,
nothing's going to change.
Forget it. Don't do it.
Hey, don't do anything.
Kang Seong-jae, follow me. Let's go.
Salute!
Gosh, I thought he was doing better lately
but there he goes again,
unable to read the room.
He must be on edge.
The place he treated like his own kingdom
is about to disappear.
I just assumed you would be
taking Min-gu with you, so...
Min-gu.
Maybe because I spoiled him
but he's gotten too big for his britches.
He doesn't just say, "Yes, sir" anymore.
The Min-gu I know
is greedy for power, not money.
Do you really see me
as someone who just uses
and discards his subordinates?
Now, you have to prove it.
That you're much better than Min-gu was.
SIX YEARS AGO
- Salute!
- Salute.
COFFEE
Drink up.
- Are you talking to me, sir?
- Who else is here besides you?
Thank you, sir. I'll enjoy it.
You were working alone last time too
and couldn't even eat properly, right?
How did you know, sir?
There's always one guy like you.
I used to be one of them.
Company Commander, why...
- Why? It's easier to be alone.
- It's not that, it's just...
I heard you were famous
even back when you were a cadet.
That you were the one
who got things done, no matter what.
Some people don't notice the unique taste
and aroma of this coffee
and just say it's bitter, right?
But if you focus just a little bit more
sometimes you can smell flowers
and sometimes you can even smell
the earth that grew the fruit.
I find myself thinking that
coffee is like the army, you know?
Oh, yes.
Getting all philosophical
over vending machine coffee, right?
- No, sir.
- It's tough, but what can you do?
You just have a sweet cup
of vending machine coffee
and forget about it. Right?
- Yes, that's right.
- Okay. I like you.
Master Sergeant Park.
Let's have some coffee.
Hey!
- What? Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol.
- I'll take three.
- What?
- You're being too greedy.
You take two.
- Deal!
The greenhorn, Kang Seong-jae.
You've summoned the one-two punch of
Ganglim Outpost, so our goal is to win.
Got it?
Hey, it's not some competition
just anyone can win, you know.
You made braised pollack once,
and now you think you're a master chef.
Hey, Kang Seong-jae. What's next?
We would like to enter
the cooking competition.
But with the situation at the outpost
don't you think this competition
is a bit of a stretch?
If we have to leave the outpost
we won't have a chance to cook anymore.
And I really want to make one last memory
with the comrades I've served with.
2025 DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
APPLICATION
Okay, I understand what you mean.
But I'm not sure if the Company Commander
will give his permission.
I'll try to put in a good word for you.
Oh, but...
This team will be okay, right?
I think we can achieve a good result.
Okay, give it your best shot.
So, have you decided on a menu?
Not yet.
Stop messing around.
- Tell her.
- Well...
Hey, what are we going to cook?
Well, isn't that
for Kang Seong-jae to decide?
What? I thought you already had
something in mind.
Well, it's my first competition.
- Hey, let's just quit. We're screwed.
- Oh, well...
First...
let's find out what dishes
our fellow outpost soldiers like
and then we can decide from there,
step-by-step.
Can't we just slap something together
real quick for them?
Gosh. That's exactly why our mess hall
has been in this state, isn't it?
The guys have food they want to eat, too.
This is so frustrating.
- I know.
- No, you don't!
- Just kidding.
- My goodness.
Gosh, what a hassle.
Just make whatever you want.
You're good at it, aren't you?
Still, if we improve on a dish
that our outpost soldiers enjoyed
wouldn't it be more meaningful?
- Man, it's cold. What?
- Salute.
Kang Seong-jae, why are you
at the Administrative Office?
He's deciding on a menu
for the cooking competition
and asked me to create a survey.
The ways he finds to boss around
his seniors are really something else.
Can't you just do it on your own?
I think it would be better
if Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun
just cheered you on.
Hey, what gives?
Things like,
"I wish we could eat this here"
or "This would be delicious."
You know, that kind of stuff.
The arancini we had during training
was really delicious.
The arancini.
- Oh, right. The arancini was delicious.
- That's right.
Hey, that was only possible
because of
my special secret-recipe rice balls.
Cheol-an, Sun-gu, Ho-yeong.
You guys know good food when you taste it.
- No wonder.
- No wonder it was so delicious.
BARRACKS 2
Hey, you guys, fill these out
and give them to me, quickly.
- Yes, sir.
"When we had the kalguksu.
It tasted good
but maybe because I got mine late
- it was soggy, which was a bummer."
- Kalguksu?
We eat rice all the time,
so naturally, noodle dishes
feel a lot more special, sir.
I see, noodle dishes.
"Looks like the secret ingredient is
having Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun
cheer from the sidelines."
I told them to suggest menu items
not write messages.
It's like a darn greeting card.
What?
Here's one. "The sujebi that
Sergeant Yoon kneaded while he was angry
was really chewy. The texture was insane."
This was when
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun was angry...
You think this is funny?
- No, sir.
- Hey, look at this.
There are guys who recognize my talent.
I'll admit,
it was definitely chewy back then.
- The seasoning was all wrong.
- What did you say?
- I thought it was chewing gum.
- Oh, that...
Since it's a three-person team
we'll need to have
a clear division of roles.
I definitely realized that
at the Officers' Mess.
We're short on time. Let's get a move on.
- Yes, sir.
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol,
since you're skilled with a knife
I'd appreciate it if you could handle
prepping the ingredients.
And as for Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun...
- Your strength...
- What? My strength? Hey.
You want me to be the cheerleader
or something? Is that it?
Since you're so good at kneading dough
with all that strength
how about we consider dishes
like sujebi or kalguksu?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Noodle dishes seem to be a big hit,
from what I've seen.
You think so?
Starting tomorrow, after our daily duties
we'll begin practicing our cooking
in earnest.
We'll decide on the menu as we practice.
If you think of anything
please feel free to share
your ideas immediately.
GANGLIM OUTPOST
- Not sure I should be involved...
- Quiet.
But why these dishes?
They're very popular with the soldiers
so I've chosen dishes
that allow the three of us
to really showcase
our individual strengths.
- Okay.
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol,
I'll need you to prep the vegetables.
Not too thick. About 5mm?
And Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun,
I'll get the broth started
so could you make the dough
while I do that?
Kneading it with power
is a skill in itself, sir.
Since we've never timed ourselves
doing everything
from prep to finish in 50 minutes
let's just think of this
as getting a feel for it
and do a practice run.
Oh, okay. Start.
- Start!
- Hold on.
- Hey, I'm in the middle.
- Middle.
- Hey, where's the flour?
- Oh, I'll go get it from the pantry.
Jeez, the flour.
Gosh, for crying out loud.
Ghost face...
Hey, Kang Seong-jae.
Is the dough supposed to be like this?
Oh, it looks like
there's a bit too much water.
Just add a bit more flour
and keep kneading. It'll be fine.
Okay.
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol, could you
please just slice this in half...
- Hey, here.
- Thank you.
SOY-BRAISED BEEF
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol,
the meat for the soy-braised beef...
Meat? I'm slicing radishes over here.
The soy-braised beef
needs to be started first.
It takes time for the flavors to marinate.
Oh, is that right?
It's okay. I'll do it.
Jeez, honestly...
- Are all the vegetables in?
- Yes, I'm just about finished.
- Sergeant Yoon.
- Yes?
Sergeant Yoon.
- Where?
- Oh, right here, sir.
- Kang Seong-jae. Now?
- Yes, right now.
The beef jeon is cold,
the seasoned radish salad is bland
the soy-braised beef
hasn't absorbed the flavor
and the sujebi is soggy.
Oh no, what am I going to do?
The cooking sequence was off
and the combination of dishes is bad too.
It's our first time trying this combo.
The fact that we even finished
is something.
If only you hadn't spilled the flour
at the start, right?
My vision was a blur,
so I got the steps mixed up, sir.
This little punk is talking nonsense.
I'm the one who fell short. I'm sorry.
I will find a solution.
You all worked so hard today.
I'll clean up, so everyone,
please go get some rest.
- No, we're not.
- Hey!
What's with him?
He's acting like if we lose,
it'll be the end of the world.
- Shut your trap.
- Go take him and wash him up.
Hero.
GANGLIM OUTPOST SHUTDOWN D-10
Nine days remaining
until the Ganglim Outpost Shutdown.
I hear Ganglim is entering
the cooking competition too.
Yes, that's right.
Seok-ho.
- Yes, Battalion Commander.
- Division Commander will be there.
It's not the kind of place
where you can just say
whatever comes to mind, right?
- What do you mean by that?
- I'm saying, is it really okay
to keep sending guys like
Kang Seong-jae to these events?
Isn't having Cho Ye-rin at Ganglim
enough trouble?
Well, it's their last chance
and it's also a way to boost
the soldiers' morale.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Battalion Commander.
I'll handle it so you won't have
anything to worry about
- Battalion Commander. Don't worry.
- It's almost over, Seok-ho.
These kids just get discharged
and it's all over for them.
Seok-ho, my Hwang Seok-ho.
You're almost there.
It's time for you to move up.
- Yes, Battalion Commander.
- Right.
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol.
The meat for the soy-braised beef...
I'm slicing radishes over here.
It's okay. I'll do it.
- Where?
- Oh, right here, sir.
- Kang Seong-jae. Now?
- Yes, right now.
With the three of us working at once
it's just too chaotic.
We're not in sync at all.
Dividing up the tasks
actually made us more inefficient.
- Is the prep done?
- Not yet, sir.
If you're done chaming the perilla
leaves, get the gastrique ready.
- Yes, sir.
We're running out of time.
Let's move faster.
- Yes, sir.
Right. After we assign the tasks...
We need someone to call out the timing.
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun.
Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol.
I know what we were missing.
- Pardon?
- Tiramisu.
Are you talking about a dessert?
- We didn't have a sweet dessert.
- You have to finish with dessert.
Oh, yes, you're right. Dessert.
And also, we divided the work
based on our specialties before.
But I actually think
that was a little inefficient.
So, I think we should keep splitting
the basic prep work like we are now
but maybe each of us should be
in charge of our own dish
from start to finish. What do you think?
So, Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun
you can handle
the most difficult and demanding task
of making the dough
and also take charge of the dessert.
And Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol.
How about you focus entirely
on the seasoned radish salad
and the beef jeon, from start to finish?
And I'll take care of everything else.
Gosh, thinking about how I'm taking on
the hardest, most difficult job...
That's a heavy weight on my shoulders.
Gosh, my shoulders.
This will work, right?
If we keep practicing like this,
I think we'll keep improving.
Yes, let's show them what
Ganglim's Army Food is all about.
Hey, are you going to stand around
talking all day
or are you going to practice?
I told you to do something about this kid.
All right, let's begin. Ready, start.
YOON DONG-HYUN: DOUGH, DESSERT
KIM KWAN-CHEOL:
SEASONED RADISH SALAD, BEEF JEON
KANG SEONG-JAE: OTHER DISHES AND HEAD CHEF
Are we finally getting in sync now?
And do some intense mental rehearsal
before bed!
Yes, but we're still on a tight schedule.
But I think we'll get much better
with practice.
You all worked hard today. Thank you.
- All right, let's head out.
- Okay.
Gosh, my wrist hurts.
GANGLIM
LEE HO-YEONG AT THE TOP
OF "PONTE DI MAESTRO"
POMODORO BRAISED BONELESS POLLACK
MOUNTAIN GREENS BIBIMBAP
DUCK CONFIT
If Corporal Lee Ho-yeong competes,
five stars won't be nearly enough.
We'll absolutely have
to do better than that.
What should I do?
Hero.
Until the Ganglim Outpost Shutdown
you have seven days left.
GANGLIM OUTPOST SHUTDOWN D-7
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
How have the food supplies been lately?
Until the day we pull out of Ganglim
will you be able to serve meals
without any issues?
Unlike before, the food supplies
are arriving without any issues.
I will do my best to provide
delicious meals until the very end.
I'm sorry, Company Commander.
The outpost is being shut down
because of me.
Come to think of it,
since you came here to Ganglim
a lot has happened, hasn't it?
Yes, sir.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Seong-jae.
Since this is the end anyway
go enter the cooking competition
and make sure you win first place.
Go show them what Ganglim is made of.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
I will be sure to come back
with a good result.
Good work.
Thanks to you, things went smoothly.
Since this is the end anyway
go enter the cooking competition
and make sure you win first place.
Okay.
For now, I'll just focus
on the competition.
What's this?
You cleaned everything up already?
Jeez, I told you I'd help.
Sergeant Yoon, are you making him
do all the work
just because you're
in your final year of service?
- Oh, no, sir. I just finished.
- What a good kid.
So, should we practice being faster today?
Well,
the team from the Officers' Mess Hall
is going with much fancier dishes
than ours.
So I think we need to upgrade our menu.
Oh, upgrade?
How? You want me to knead the dough
with more power?
- That's not what he's talking about.
- Then what?
Well, with the dishes
we already know how to make
what if we add a fusion twist
and come up with a new menu?
Oh, right. The guys love noodle dishes.
Pasta?
How?
You want me to take the dough
and make some kalguksu nice and chewy?
What? A pasta dish
made with kalguksu noodles...
I think that could work.
- What's gotten into the devil chef?
- What did you say, punk?
You have acquired a new recipe.
Gochujang Ragu Pasta
using kalguksu noodles.
Successfully creating a fusion dish
will earn you an extra star.
- Hey, Kang Seong-jae!
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Did my crazy idea
blow your mind or something?
Oh, no, sir.
Would you like to taste-test it right now?
Yes! Let's get it!
- Go!
- Come on!
Yes!
- Hey, Kang Seong-jae.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
Why are you pushing yourself so hard
when we're all about to split up anyway?
Oh, it's not like that.
It's just that all of you seniors
treated me so well.
And I'm really sad to see it end.
I mean, I was pretty good to you.
Man, I wonder what position
I'll get when I transfer.
Do you want to keep being a cook?
- It's tough, right?
- Well...
Not at all.
At first, waking up early was hard
and the knife work, the hot fire...
it was all so new and difficult.
But I gradually got better
and watching our outpost soldiers
enjoy the food I made
gave me this strange, wonderful feeling.
I thought military life would just be hard
but I found it so rewarding.
I wanted to use this opportunity
to really practice and get good
at cooking before I left.
- So it's a real shame.
- Your talent is a waste.
You should tell them
that you want to keep being a cook
when you transfer to the battalion.
- For the Officers' Mess, if you can.
- Well...
But...
I think the Battalion Commander
has a bad impression of me.
Oh, right.
You made him flustered
at the Officers' Mess
talking about the food supply, didn't you?
- Yes, that's right.
- That must be awkward.
No, wait. Who knows?
You could go to the cooking competition
the Division Commander tries your food
and says, "Wait, we're closing the outpost
that has a soldier this amazing?
Battalion Commander, shape up your unit."
Then we might not have to
transfer after all!
- Is that even possible?
- You wish.
- Oh, I see.
- Hey, get back to peeling.
- Yes, sir.
- Man, it's cold.
Well, now...
This will be our last meal
at the Ganglim Outpost.
My soldiers, you've all worked so hard.
- You've worked hard too, sir.
- Right.
Like the Master Sergeant said,
you've all endured a lot.
Since this is our last meal at the outpost
let's eat up and be strong.
Let's make sure we finish everything
on a high note.
- Got it?
- Yes, ma'am!
- Let's eat.
- Enjoy your meal.
My goodness.
The soup is surprisingly good today, sir.
Don't bullshit me, you punk.
At least make it believable.
- Wait!
- One second!
This is the secret
to getting rid of the smell.
Come on, light.
Have a safe trip, sir!
MOUNTAIN GREENS BIBIMBAP
- What's wrong with everyone?
- But I didn't make it spicy.
With every single bite
I get all emotional for some reason.
Jeez, am I getting sentimental
in my old age?
- I thought it was just me.
- It feels weirdly like leaving home.
Thinking that I won't get to eat
Kang Seong-jae's food
for the rest of my service...
It is kind of a bummer, sir.
Kang Seong-jae.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
You better go there and do well.
You hear me?
You're representing
our proud Ganglim Outpost
so winning is your only option. Got it?
Yes, sir. Since you believe in me,
I'll give it my all.
All right, good.
What's with the somber mood?
I guess they've all grown attached.
Enjoy your meal, Company Commander.
Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
- I enjoyed this final meal.
- That was really good.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you for all your hard work.
- Thank you.
- It was so good.
- For all the outpost soldiers...
Cooking that makes them feel
right at home.
That might be the kind of cooking
we need right now.
Hero.
Only one day remains until
the Ganglim Outpost is closed.
29TH DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
Gosh, these guys look intense.
- They're just trying to act tough.
- Then why are you shaking so much?
It's because I lifted heavy yesterday.
- I'm not nervous.
- You got everything, right?
Yes. I've packed
the cooking equipment and everything.
- What?
- Is that the guy you talked about?
Man, he looks way more arrogant
than I thought.
It's his well-founded confidence
that's even scarier.
Let's not get intimidated.
- We're not half bad when we team up.
- Sure!
- Let's go.
Hey, don't waste your energy.
Let's go.
29TH DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
1ST BATTALION, GANGLIM OUTPOST
ROSE-KNIFE
Now, the 29th Division Cooking Competition
will begin.
Let me introduce our panel of judges.
Our 29th Division's
gentle and warm leader.
Division Commander Kim In-tae.
A round of applause!
Good luck!
GOURMET RATING
The fiercely charismatic gourmet.
60th Regimental Commander Bae Won-young.
Good luck, 29th Division!
Ensuring warriors are fed.
- Good luck!
- Battalion Commander Baek Chun-ik.
GOURMET RATING
Now, let's introduce the four teams
participating in this competition.
- Artillery Regiment Mess Hall.
- Salute!
- The 3rd Infantry Regiment Mess Hall.
And...
joined by a culinary prodigy
the whole world is watching
the 60th Regiment, 1st Battalion
Officers' Mess.
- Sir!
- And finally
the dark horse that moved an assemblyman.
The Ganglim Outpost Mess Hall.
- Salute!
Salute.
- At ease!
- Our soldiers.
Do you know how much money is allocated
for one hearty meal for our soldiers?
Today's mission is called
Happiness for 4,500 Won!
In just 50 minutes, with exactly 4,500 won
you must present a dish
that perfectly suits the palates
of our judges.
- Huddle up.
- Yes.
Let's show them a textbook example
of a French plate.
I'll handle the main dish,
the Pork Medallion.
They're making
"Pork something-or-other" over there.
I can't even tell
what it is they're making.
We just need to do well,
just as we prepared.
- I'm putting my faith in you two.
- If Kang Seong-jae is this sure
then I'll just trust you two
and follow along.
Right, Kang Seong-jae is the one
we have to trust and rely on.
- Let's go!
- Now
- please start cooking!
- Go, Ganglim!
We'll finish prepping the panna cotta
in three minutes
and go straight to boiling.
I'll finish the veggie prep
in four minutes.
Finish in three minutes
and go help Yong-hoon.
Yes, sir.
- Corporal Kim Kwan-cheol.
- Yes?
- Good. I'm starting on the radishes.
- Okay, starting on the dough.
I'll start on the braise
once the ingredients are prepped.
- Okay!
Now 30 minutes remaining.
Everyone's hands are moving
faster and faster.
- Stir it a little more.
- Yes, sir.
Okay.
All right,
I'll start crushing the military biscuits.
If you could just cut down
on the small mistakes...
Let's rally one more time.
- Okay, let's do this!
- Let's do this!
RESTING
Resting complete.
Sergeant Yoon Dong-hyun,
I think the dough is done resting.
Yes!
Hey, Seong-jae! The noodles came out.
Look at them!
Nice!
Yes!
- I ground it up fine, didn't I?
- Gosh, with this
the tiramisu should turn out really moist.
Man, I feel like I could smash up all the
military biscuits in the world. You know?
Isn't it a little late
to be getting the hang of it?
- What, sad to see me go?
- I think you should stay in the army.
You punk, I will just...
Gochujang Ragu Pasta.
One star has been added
for a successful fusion dish.
- Yes!
- We still have plenty of time.
This is going smoother than I thought.
I think it's all thanks to you two
working so hard.
- Hey!
- Yes.
The Pork Medallion,
made by Corporal Lee Ho-yeong.
PORK MEDALLION
A seven-star dish has been completed.
The moment I thought we had made it
seven stars were twinkling before my eyes.
Hey, what's wrong?
- Kang Seong-jae!
- Oh, uh, it's nothing.
- Snap out of it.
- Right.
GOCHUJANG RAGU PASTA
Even when I used my abilities
to their fullest...
I was faced with an existence
I could never surpass.
And I felt myself shrinking into nothing.
Kang Seong-jae!
- Private First Class Kang Seong-jae.
- We have to finish this.
- Get a hold of yourself.
- Oh, yes, sir.
Only then did I realize...
that I...
had willingly thrown myself
into a game I could never win.
I have now been utterly defeated.
The final dish has been completed.
Half a star for the combination
with the other dishes.
And another half a star is added
for the harmony with your comrades
completing the Gochujang Ragu Pasta set
as a seven-star dish.
GOCHUJANG RAGU PASTA
WITH ULTIMATE COMBINATION
29TH DIVISION COOKING COMPETITION
Stop! Everyone, hands off your stations.
Now, let's have a round of applause
for our hard-working soldiers.
We have prepared
a French-style Pork Medallion.
You can enjoy it
with the Dijon mustard sauce
and finish with the yogurt panna cotta
for dessert. Please enjoy it.
It's so tender
the knife just glides through.
Amazing.
Oh, very good.
The meat just melts on your tongue.
Yes. This has a real touch of class.
I feel like a king.
The flavor of this sauce.
Can't you feel the French breeze?
Hello!
A dish like this couldn't have been easy
to make in the army.
How did they even come up with this?
I wanted to challenge the stereotype
that military food has to be simple.
I wanted to serve a dish that would
make them feel like honored guests.
As expected of a champion.
You're really something else.
- That was delicious.
- Thank you.
Me too.
Impressive.
Did you make this pasta dish
with kalguksu noodles?
Yes, I made a ragu sauce using gochujang
and made the pasta
with hand-kneaded noodles.
I also prepared
some citron seasoned radish salad
- and beef jeon on the side.
- What's this stone for?
I placed a heated stone underneath
to keep the beef jeon warm.
And if you finish with the sweet
military biscuit tiramisu for dessert
it will be the perfect meal.
- Enough talk. Let's dig in.
- Yes.
This tastes just like the fancy restaurant
pasta I had on my honeymoon.
I can't believe
I'm eating this in the army.
Impressive.
Waiter!
Hey, don't make it too salty.
- I thought this was Italy.
- Italy, my foot.
When food gets too rich,
nothing beats gochujang.
Yes, this is it.
It's not just a sophisticated flavor.
It's this spicy gochujang flavor
that really hits the spot!
Yes!
I thought the winner of this match
was already decided
but this makes it so hard.
- Division Commander.
- Yes?
Oh. It's a good kind of spicy.
The seasoning is perfectly subtle.
It's great.
- Division Commander.
- Yes?
- The 3rd Infantry Regiment.
- Oh, right.
Military biscuit tiramisu.
What? Is that his reaction?
I can't read
the Division Commander's expression.
Five minutes
until Ganglim Outpost Shutdown.
That's the remaining time.
GANGLIM OUTPOST SHUTDOWN
All right, the scores
have all been tallied.
I'm very excited to see
which team will be the winner.
And now, I will announce the results.
In fourth place...
is the Artillery Regiment
with their tuna rice bowl.
The judges said the knife skills
were excellent, but it was too salty.
Third place
is the 3rd Infantry Regiment with
the shrimp-stuffed eggplant over rice.
The batter was excellent
but the shrimp was a bit undercooked.
Now, only two teams remain.
Both from the 1st Battalion.
The Officers' Mess
and the Ganglim Outpost.
And now, for the results.
First place is...
The 1st Battalion...
- The Officers' Mess! Congratulations!
- Nice!
Sergeant Yoon, look at Seong-jae.
- Second place is great. Chin up.
- Yes, sir.
And Ganglim Outpost,
4th Company, 1st Battalion is
- tied for first place! Congratulations!
- What?
- We did?!
Look at how happy they are.
We tied with Ganglim for first place?
No way. Is this for real?
We did it!
- So why isn't the Quest complete?
- Well...
It was an incredibly difficult decision.
Both teams presented wonderful dishes
and while the Officers' Mess's score
was slightly higher
because it was more suitable
for military meals
the Ganglim Outpost received bonus points
resulting in a tie between the two teams.
So, after a discussion among the judges
we've decided to hold
a final one-on-one showdown
- to determine the ultimate winner.
- What?
What? I thought it was over.
GANGLIM OUTPOST SHUTDOWN
Hero.
You have failed to complete the Quest.
All skills and recipes will disappear.
The Chef's Path will now end.
All right, this competition isn't
a team battle. It's an individual one
a one-on-one showdown.
What?
One representative soldier from each team
will have 50 minutes to complete a dish.
A representative?
- Seong-jae, get ready. You got this!
- Let's make sure we win this time.
Show them what you got.
Representatives, please step forward!
Come on, walk tall. Go!
It all vanished in an instant.
Everything I gained at Ganglim.
The recipes
the eyes that could see
through ingredients
and...
all the potential
of what I could have become.
All the sensations I felt at my fingertips
felt completely empty.
It was as if
I had gone back to the day
I first held a knife.
THE LEGEND OF KITCHEN SOLDIER
We will now begin
the final one-on-one showdown.
- What can I do without my status window?
- Come on...
Is it all over? Just start over.
For this last one, without any regrets
I hope you'll make the dish
you really want to make.
I need a deep, rich umami flavor.
- Five minutes remaining.
- Cooking is all about heart! Heart!
One minute remaining.
And the final result is...